[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
* *
**
- Blllllaaaahhhh!
- 啦啦啦啦啦！
Oh! Oh!
哦！哦！
Whoa...
[tearing sound]
哇...
[撕裂声]
Oh ha!
哦哈！
Whoo!
[indistinct shouting]
呼！
[隐隐约约的喊叫]
- Squidward. What do you
think the nurse
- 章鱼哥。你做什么
认为护士
is doing to him
in there?
对他做的事
在那里？
- It's called a "checkup."
- 这就是所谓的“检查”。
It's an invasion
of your personal space
这是一次入侵
您的个人空间
that's good for you.
这对你有好处。
- Aaaaahhhh!
- 啊啊啊！
- [gasp]
- Ah!
- [喘气]
- 啊！
- [frightened sounds]
- [害怕的声音]
Whoa!
哇！
- Eee...
[SpongeBob shouting]
- 呃…
[海绵宝宝大喊]
[chomping]
[咀嚼]
Eee--aah!
哎呀——啊啊！
[light music]
[轻音乐]
[nonsense sounds]
[胡言乱语的声音]
[giggling]
[咯咯笑]
- Sir, please hold still.
- 先生，请保持不动。
I need to check
your reflexes.
我需要检查
你的反应。
- Sorry, nurse lady.
I've never had a checkup before.
- 对不起，护士小姐。
我以前从来没有做过检查。
It's so much fun!
太有趣了！
[dink]
[丁克]
[high-pitched horn squeal]
[高亢的喇叭声]
- [sighs]
You seem fine...
- [叹气]
你看起来很好...
physically, at least.
至少在身体上是这样。
Congratulations.
You pass.
恭喜。
你通过了。
- Wow! Imagine
if it was this easy
- 哇！想象一下
如果这么简单的话
to get your boating
license!
去划船
许可证！
- Eh. The world
shudders at the thought.
- 呃。世界
一想到这里就不寒而栗。
- Mr. Tentacles?!
- 触手先生？！
- Finally!
Let's get this over with!
- 最后！
让我们结束这一切吧！
- [whimpering]
Ooh...
- [呜咽]
哦...
So, Boy-o...
how was it in there?
那么，小男孩...
那里怎么样？
Anything I should be...
terrified of?
任何我应该...
害怕什么？
- Oh, no, Mr. Krabs!
Getting a checkup is the best!
- 哦，不，蟹老板！
去检查一下是最好的！
The nurse poked me
and prodded me
护士戳我
并刺激我
and jabbed me...
[bell rings]
并戳了我...
[铃声响起]
and pulled me
and twisted me.
并拉了我
并扭曲了我。
And--
- Okay, okay.
还有——
- 好吧，好吧。
That's enough.
[giggles]
这就够了。
[咯咯笑]
- You want me to what?
- 你要我做什么？
- [whimpering]
Ooh...
- [呜咽]
哦...
- Fill this, please.
- 请填写这个。
- Hmph.
[mumbling]
- 哼。
[咕哝]
Could I get a little
privacy?
我可以得到一点吗
隐私？
[mumbling]
[咕哝]
[liquid whooshing]
[液体嘶嘶声]
- Hmm...
good color.
- 嗯...
颜色好。
Solid line fidelity.
实线保真度。
The ink is a little
thick, though.
墨水有点
不过，很厚。
- Hey!
- You just need to drink
- 嘿！
- 你只需要喝点酒
more water.
更多的水。
You pass.
你通过了。
- Is there a...
- 有没有一个...
Eugene Krabs?!
尤金·克拉布斯？！
- Your turn, Mr. K.
- 轮到你了，K先生
- [squeaks, panting]
- [吱吱声，气喘吁吁]
[dramatic music]
[戏剧音乐]
[bottle clatters]
[瓶子碰撞声]
- Ha ha.
Looks like the old man
- 哈哈。
看起来像老头
is scared of getting
his checkup.
害怕得到
他的检查。
- This is no
laughing matter!
- 这不是
笑的事！
Every employee
must get their checkup...
每一位员工
必须接受他们的检查...
or the restaurant
will be closed--
或餐厅
将被关闭——
under orders of the Bikini
Bottom Better Business Bureau.
在比基尼的命令下
底层商业改善局。
- [gasps]
Not the...B.B.B.B.B!
- [喘气]
不是……B.B.B.B.B！
- You heard her.
- 你听到她的声音了。
The...bbbbbbbb!
那个...bbbbbbbb！
- Perhaps we could reach
some sort of understanding.
- 也许我们可以到达
某种理解。
- Oh, oh, I know!
- 哦，哦，我知道！
We'll give Mr. Krabs
his checkup over the weekend
我们会给蟹老板
他周末检查
and you just pick up
the results on Monday.
你只需拿起
周一出结果。
heavenly chorus: * Ahh *
- [singsong] Everybody wins!
天堂合唱：*啊*
- [单曲] 每个人都赢了！
- I was just gonna bribe her.
[cash register dings]
- 我只是想贿赂她
[收银机叮叮声]
- Monday works.
- 周一上班。
- Yay! We get to spend
the weekend together!
- 耶！我们可以花
一起过周末！
- [humming]
Dodged that bullet!
- [嗡嗡声]
躲过了那颗子弹！
- [gasps]
He's coming!
- [喘气]
他来了！
- It says here the first
part of Krab's exam
- 这里说的是第一个
Krab 考试的一部分
is the pinch test.
是捏测试。
We just need to do it
我们只需要这样做
in a way he doesn't know
he's being tested!
以他不知道的方式
他正在接受考验！
- Way ahead a ya!
- 遥遥领先啊！
We'll make him an offer
he can't resist!
我们会给他报价
他无法抗拒！
- "Free money inside."
- “里面有免费的钱。”
Ha. Not bad.
哈。不错。
- Come on, before he sees us!
- 快点，在他看到我们之前！
- [humming]
- [嗡嗡声]
Huh? Free money, hey?
啊？免费的钱，嘿？
[chuckles]
Don't mind if I do!
[笑声]
如果我这样做的话，请不要介意！
Where's that money?
那些钱在哪里？
I'm not feeling any money!
我没感觉有钱啊！
[snap, snap, snap, snap]
- Ooh! Ey! Ah! Ehh!
[啪，啪，啪，啪]
- 哦！哎呀！啊!呃！
- [growls]
- [咆哮]
[snap snap]
[啪啪啪]
- Okay. I brought
plenty of things
- 好的。我带来了
很多东西
for Mr. Krabs to pinch--
让蟹老板捏——
a pinch of salt--
少许盐——
Aah!
[snap]
啊啊！
[折断]
[moans]
[呻吟声]
A baby's cheek!
婴儿的脸颊！
[baby cooing]
[婴儿咕咕声]
[snap]
[baby cooing]
[啪]
[婴儿咕咕声]
[electronic sizzling]
[电子滋滋声]
Lucky that was a robot body.
幸运的是，那是一个机器人身体。
- SpongeBob,
quit fooling around!
- 海绵宝宝，
别胡闹了！
Ow!
[moaning]
噢！
[呻吟]
We need to test his ability
to pinch something tough,
我们需要测试他的能力
捏一些坚硬的东西，
you ninny!
- Tough, huh?
你这个笨蛋！
- 很难吧？
Gosh, the toughest thing
I can think of
天哪，最难的事
我能想到
is...Mr. Krabs himself!
是……先生。蟹蟹本人！
[snap]
- [groaning]
[啪]
- [呻吟]
[shrill scream]
Ohhh!
[尖叫声]
哦哦！
Ooh-ooh-ooh-ooh!
哦哦哦！
Me achin' pinchers!
我好痛啊！
And I didn't even
get any money!
而我什至没有
得到任何钱！
[coin clatters]
[硬币碰撞声]
Hee hee! A penny!
嘻嘻！一分钱！
It's me lucky day!
[giggling]
这是我的幸运日！
[咯咯笑]
- Pinch test failed.
- 挤压测试失败。
Well, maybe he'll do better
on the eye stalk test.
好吧，也许他会做得更好
关于眼柄测试。
[light music]
[轻音乐]
* *
**
- Free suits?
Oh, boy!
- 免费套装？
哦，孩子！
- Welcome, sir.
I--Oh--oh--Uh--shee--
- 欢迎，先生。
我--哦--哦--呃--嘘--
Step up here, and we'll begin.
站到这里，我们就开始吧。
[quietly] Squidward, do you
have the measuring tape?
[小声]章鱼哥，你吗？
有卷尺吗？
Just grabbing
some measurements...
只是抓
一些测量...
Oh!
哦！
- Sir, try to keep still.
- 先生，请保持安静。
[tock, tock, tock, tock]
[嘟嘟，嘟嘟，嘟嘟，嘟嘟]
[crunch]
- Whoa, there!
[紧缩]
- 哇，在那里！
Don't you need
some other measurements?
你不需要吗
其他一些测量？
I mean, how 'bout me inseam?
我的意思是，我的内缝怎么样？
[jangling]
[叮叮当当]
- Uh, no, you can
put that away, sir.
- 呃，不，你可以
把它收起来，先生。
I'm almost done.
我快完成了。
[light music]
[轻音乐]
- Aah! That's it!
- 啊啊！就是这样！
Get off me,
you terrible tailor!
从我身上下来，
你这个可怕的裁缝！
- Tell your friends about us!
- Not likely!
- 向您的朋友介绍我们！
- 不太可能！
- How'd he do?
- Oh, he didn't make the cut.
- 他怎么样？
- 哦，他没有晋级。
- Of course.
Up next, it says
- 当然。
接下来，它说
we have to get
an X-ray of him.
我们必须得到
他的X光片
Any ideas?
- I do have one plan
有什么想法吗？
- 我确实有一个计划
that might work.
这可能有用。
* *
**
- [grunts]
- Hello there, sir!
- [咕哝]
- 你好，先生！
Are you rightfully afraid
of your own mortality?
你有理由害怕吗
你自己的死亡率？
Wanna make sure
that when you're gone,
想确定一下
当你离开时，
you are not forgotten?
Well, step on up
你是不是被遗忘了？
嗯，继续往上走
and marvel at the latest
technological wonder--
并惊叹于最新的
科技奇迹——
photography!
Preserve your precious punim
摄影！
保护你珍贵的普宁
for generations to come!
为了子孙后代！
Aah...whaaa...
啊啊……哇啊……
Conquer time itself
at absolutely no charge to you!
征服时间本身
绝对不向您收取任何费用！
- No charge, hey?
[spits]
- 不收费，嘿？
[吐口水]
Well...I am very
"photogeneric."
嗯……我很
“上镜。”
Let's see...
让我们来看看...
how do you start this thing?
你如何开始这件事？
Oh! Here we go!
哦！开始了！
[X-ray machine humming]
[X光机嗡嗡声]
Hoo! Gettin' kinda hot
in here!
呼！有点热
在这里！
[chuckles]
[笑声]
Should my underwear
be on fire?
我的内衣应该
着火了吗？
- How many X-rays
of Mr. Krabs do we need?
- 多少次X光检查
我们需要蟹老板吗？
- Just one. How many
did you set it to take?
- 只有一个。有多少
你把它设置为采取吗？
- 25...
thousand?
千？
- Uh...this is getting
a little...[gibberish]
- 呃...这越来越
有点……[胡言乱语]
Eh...thank you.
呃……谢谢你。
No more pictures, please.
请不要再发照片了。
[mumbling, whimpering]
[咕哝，呜咽]
[bones clattering]
- Squidward, is his skeleton
[骨头嘎嘎作响]
- 章鱼哥，是他的骷髅
supposed to just
fall apart like that?
应该只是
就这样崩溃了？
- Not at all.
- 一点也不。
On to the next test.
进入下一个测试。
- [moaning]
- [呻吟]
Oh...oh...
哦...哦...
Oh, what a day.
哦，多么美好的一天啊。
- Hey, man, you look like
you've had a rough day.
- 嘿，伙计，你看起来像
你这一天过得很艰难。
How'd ya like to chill out
with a nice massage?
你想放松一下吗
有很好的按摩吗？
It's free.
它是免费的。
- Free, huh?
- 免费，是吧？
- Free.
- Eh. Okay.
- 自由的。
- 呃。好的。
Let's get this over with.
让我们结束这一切吧。
- Remember, this is
the cold-blooded test.
-记住，这是
冷血的考验。
Just take his temperature.
量一下他的体温就可以了。
- You got it, best friend.
- 你明白了，最好的朋友。
- Don't call me that.
- 别这么叫我。
- Boop!
- [stammers] Don't you do that!
- 噗！
- [结巴]你别这么做！
- I'm ready!
- 我准备好了！
- All right, man,
let's see if we can, like,
- 好吧，伙计，
让我们看看是否可以，比如
work out some of this
tension.
解决一些这个问题
紧张。
- Why, you--
Oh, no, no, no, no, no!
- 为什么，你--
噢，不，不，不，不，不！
- [panting]
- [气喘吁吁]
- How's the cold-blooded
test going?
- 冷血是怎样的
测试进行吗？
- Great! He's in the freezer
right now.
- 伟大的！他在冰箱里
现在。
- SpongeBob, you moron!
Cold-blooded means your body
- 海绵宝宝，你这个白痴！
冷血意味着你的身体
is the same temperature
as the water around it--
是相同的温度
就像它周围的水一样——
not that you're actually cold!
并不是说你真的很冷！
- [gasps]
[teeth chattering]
- [喘气]
[牙齿打战]
[whimpering]
[呜咽]
Squidward?
章鱼哥？
Whyyyyyy?
为什么yyyyy？
- Oh, Mr. Krabs,
I'm so sorry!
-哦，蟹老板先生，
我很抱歉！
We had to give you your physical
without you knowing,
我们必须给你你的身体
在你不知道的情况下，
or the Krusty Krab
woulda been shut down,
或蟹堡王
会被关闭，
and I'd have to get
a real job!
我必须得到
一份真正的工作！
- All right!
Final test!
- 好的！
最终测试！
Shell durability!
外壳耐用！
Wha-hah!
哇哈！
- No, no, no, no, no, no!
- 不，不，不，不，不，不！
[stammering]
[结巴]
[muffled, lisping] Now you see
why I don't like checkups?
[低沉，口齿不清]现在你明白了
为什么我不喜欢检查？
[sobbing]
[抽泣]
- Don't worry, Mr. Krabs.
- 别担心，蟹老板。
Yes, you failed
every test today,
是的，你失败了
今天的每一次考试，
but Squidward and I
will whip you into shape,
但章鱼哥和我
会鞭打你塑造形状，
even if it takes
the rest of the weekend!
即使需要
周末剩下的时间！
- [sobbing]
- [抽泣]
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
- Let's kick it up a notch!
- 让我们更上一层楼吧！
- [grunting]
- [咕哝]
Eeeee!
哎呀！
Guuuuuuhhhh!
咕咕咕啊啊啊！
Whoa--no!
哇——不！
[whimpering]
[呜咽]
Aah...aah!
啊啊……啊啊！
[panting]
[气喘吁吁]
[beep beep]
[嘟嘟]
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
[hyperventilating]
[换气过度]
[stammering]
Oh--oh--no--oh, jeez--ohh!
[结巴]
哦——哦——不——哦，天哪——哦！
- I don't know what
we did wrong, Squidward.
- 我不知道什么
我们做错了，章鱼哥。
Mr. Krabs
looks worse than before!
蟹老板先生
看起来比以前更糟糕了！
- [moaning]
- [呻吟]
- I guess that nurse is gonna
close the Krusty Krab after all.
- 我猜那个护士会
毕竟关掉蟹堡王吧。
I wish I could say
我希望我能说
it's been a pleasure
working with you.
很高兴
和你一起工作。
- Oh, Squidward,
I'll miss you too!
-哦，章鱼哥，
我也会想念你的！
[sobbing]
[抽泣]
- Quit yer blubberin', boy.
- 别再哭了，孩子。
Me body may be mush,
but me mind's sharp as a tack!
我的身体可能很软弱，
但我的头脑非常敏锐！
And I...have a plan.
我……有一个计划。
[light music]
[轻音乐]
- Good morning!
- 早上好！
I assume your boss
passed his physical?
我假设你的老板
通过了他的体检吗？
- Oh, um...yes.
Of course he did.
- 哦，嗯...是的。
他当然做到了。
Um, unfortunately,
our results were--
嗯，不幸的是，
我们的结果是——
- Uh, eaten!
- Yeah, yeah.
- 呃，吃饱了！
- 是啊是啊。
Um, anyway,
we thought you could
嗯，无论如何，
我们认为你可以
give old Mr. K
another exam yourself.
给老K先生
自己再做一次考试。
He's in his office.
他在他的办公室里。
- Hmm...
- 唔...
Very well.
很好。
[drilling sound, horn honks,
thud, cracking]
[钻孔声、喇叭声、
砰的一声，破裂]
Mr. Krabs...
蟹老板...
not only did you
pass your exam,
你不仅
通过考试，
you might be the most
你可能是最
astonishingly excellent physical
specimen I've ever seen!
身体素质惊人的优秀
我见过的标本！
[laughs]
both: Whew!
[笑]
两人：唷！
- My name is Mr. Krabs,
- 我叫蟹老板先生
and I love money!
我爱钱！
- Yes. You said so several times
during the examination.
- 是的。你说过好几次了
考试期间。
- [forced laugh]
Ack, ack, ack, ack, ack,
- [强笑]
确认，确认，确认，确认，确认，
- I suppose I won't need to
close your restaurant today.
- 我想我不需要
今天关闭您的餐厅。
See you next year.
明年见。
- Whoo-hoo!
We did it, boys!
- 呼呼！
我们做到了，孩子们！
The Krusty Krab
lives to see another day!
蟹堡王
活着就是为了再见到另一天！
Three cheers
for a successful ruse!
三声欢呼
为了成功的诡计！
- Let's just make it one.
- 让我们合而为一吧。
both: Hip, hip, hooray!
两者：时髦，时髦，万岁！
- So, you said there would be
- 所以，你说会有
some money in this for me?
- [squeals]
给我一些钱吗？
- [尖叫声]
* *
**
[crazed laughter]
[glass shatters]
[疯狂的笑声]
[玻璃碎裂]
- You'll never get me money!
- 你永远不会给我钱！
Ah ha ha ha ha ha!
啊哈哈哈哈哈哈！